# TSAI NEI(NI) YUAN

https://github.com/tsainei +41 763802491 - hi@tsainei.com





Passionate fullstack developer with experience using Ruby, JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS to build all aspects of the user experience and user interface for client-facing landing pages. Specialize in using React.js and Vue.js to build e-commerce sites.

I'm most experienced in **React.js** and **Javascript**.

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

Birthday: 10.09.1992Nationality: Spain

Work Permit: B-permit (EU/EFTA)

Civil Status: Married

• Address: Schönauweg, 1, Adliswil 8134

#### **EXPERIENCE**

01.10.2021 - NOW

**FRONT-END DEVELOPER** (Zurich, Switzerland)

Work on personal projects and learn these skills:

- German(A1)
- Angular
- Typescript
- Python

01.2020 - 30.09.2021

MARKETING SPECIALIST, SWAG/CYREK (Remote, Taipei, Taiwan)

SWAG is the largest entertaining platform in Asia, serving more than 2 million customers a month. It has users worldwide and the company is expanding rapidly.

- Automate marketing data ingestion by creating a periodic job that imports data from multiple sources using Google Analytics APIs, Puppeteer and node.js, resulting in 90 mins of error-prone manual work saved per day.
- Interface with Google sheets API to export the data for other departments.
- Create a self-service portal using React.js that allows Swaggers to calculate and predict their income.
- Set up recruitment websites in multiple languages.
- Write a command line application to add watermarks in bulk to social media videos and pictures that intelligently selects optimal size, position and color to maximize contrast.

01.2017 - 12.2017 FREELANCE TRANSLATOR,

CHINESE SAFE PATIENT HANDLING & MOVEMENT ASSOCIATION (Taipei, Taiwan)

Translate documents for the association from Mandarin to English and vice versa.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **11-04.2022-10.06.2022 LE WAGON BOOTCAMP** (Zurich, Switzerland)

- Learn Ruby, Ruby on Rails, OOP, MVC model, Javascript, HTML, CSS...
- Build group project

#### 09.2012-2017

#### BACHELOR OF ETHNOLOGY, National ChengChi University(Taipei, Taiwan)

- Minored in Arabic language and culture
- Won 1st Prize Of Reader's Digest 150 Words Small Essay Competition
- 2014 won the summer school scholarship of Czech Republic
- 2015 won the summer school scholarship of Hungary

#### 2016-2017

## INTERNATIONAL RELATIONS, Rey Juan Carlos University (Madrid, Spain)

Exchange student in the department of International Relations.

## **GENERAL COMMUNICATION & ABILITIES**

- Possess a positive, energetic and professional attitude.
- Achieving goals, creative/strategic thinking and problem solving.
- Demonstrating ability to work and perform at the highest standards in complex and demanding environment.
- Excellent ethics, hardworking, focus minded and sound organizational ability.
- Flexible to change with excellent planning and execution skills and works well within the constraints and tight deadlines.

#### SKILLS

- Programming Skills: JavaScript, ReactJS, Vue.js, Typescript & Ruby
- Language Skills:
  Mandarin(Native),
  English(TOEFL:100), Spanish(B2),
  Arabic(A2) & German(A1)